Guide to the National Education Association-Film, Audio, and Video records, 1938-2011 NEA1010.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Conventions, 1955-2001; Series 1; 85 Linear Feet
  - Interview - Ryor-Ford-Carter, ca. 1976-1980; Series 1; Herndon, Terry; Ryor, John; Carter, Jimmy, President, 1924-; Magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. (Box 3688, Folder 1)
  - January, 1964, Series 1; audio reel-to-reel (Box 3897, Folder 8)
  - Johnathan Kozel - 1992 NEA RA Address, Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3976, Folder 4)
  - J. Richard Suchman - Spokane Conference 1966 - Methods of Learning - Master - Some on Side 2, Series 1; # 19 3 3/4 (Box 3558, Folder 8)
  - Kalkaska Closing Vigil Ceremony, March 24, 1993; Series 1 (Box 3966, Folder 6)
  - Keith & Lydia's Most Excellent Adventure - National Conference Spring '96, April 13, 1996; Series 3 (Box 3990, Folder 2)
  - Keith & Lydia's Most Excellent Adventure - National Conference Spring 1996, April 13, 1996; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4100, Folder 6)
  - Keith Geiger - 1992 NEA RA Address, Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3976, Folder 5)
  - Margaret S. Woods - Spokane Regional Conference 1966 - 2:30 - A Childs Legacy, January 27, 1966; Series 1; 3 3/4 IPS Full Track (Box 3558, Folder 9)
  - Mary Futrell: 1998 RA, July 21, 1998; Series 1 (Box 4634, Folder 9)
  - Mary Hatwood Futrell 1992 NEA Representative Assembly Address, Series 1 (Box 3967, Folder 4)
  - Mary Hatwood Futrell at '92 NEA R.A., July 14, 1992; Series 1; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 6)
  - "Mathematics" – G. Baley Price, exec. sec. Conference Board of Mathematical Sciences, Washington, DC Tuesday, March 27, 1:30 pm, Undated; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3884, Folder 4)
  - MEA/MFT 1995 Educator's Conference Keynote Address - Geiger/Shanker, October 19, 1995; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3976, Folder 6)
  - Meeting of the Board of Directors of the NEA, President Helen Bain, Friday AM Session, 4/30/71, April 30, 1971; Series 1; Bain, Helen; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. Includes handwritten notes from meeting. (Box 3771, Folder 8)
  - "Music" – Eugene W. Truth, Assoc. Prof. of Music Educ., U. of Mich. Tuesday, March 27, 1:30 pm, Undated; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3884, Folder 5)
  - National Conference 'Children in America's Schools", April 3, 1997; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3975, Folder 5)
  - National Conference Orlando "Keith & Suzie" Tape 1, March 29, 1996; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3968, Folder 2)
  - National Conference Orlando "Keith & Suzie" Tape 2, March 29, 1996; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3968, Folder 3)
  - National Conference Orlando "Keith Geiger's Conclusion", March 29, 1996; Series 1 (Box 3967, Folder 10)
  - National Conference Orlando "Keith Geiger's Intro", March 29, 1996; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3968, Folder 1)
  - National Education Association: 1993 RA Staff Party, July 5, 1993; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4024, Folder 3)
  - National Education Association: Recap of the 124th NEA - RA, July 16, 1986; Series 1; VHS videocassette, 6:03. (Box 3828, Folder 5)
  - NCAE Press Conference- Raleigh, North Carolina, 2006; Series 1; DVD (Box 4015, Folder 9)
  - NCI Teacher TV RA Breaks '93, June 24, 1993; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4024, Folder 4)
  - NCI / Teacher TV - Representative Assembly Breaks, June 24, 1993; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3968, Folder 5)
  - NEA '76 Annual Meeting: President John Ryor, 1976; Series 1; Audio cassette. (Box 3682, Folder 43)
  - NEA 115th Annual Meeting (1977) Ryor/Herndon, Series 1; Audio cassette. (Box 3682, Folder 25)
  - NEA 115th Annual Meeting - Hubert Humphrey, NEA's Friend of Education, 1977, Cassette Master Looped, July 1977; Series 1; Humphrey, Hubert H.; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. (Box 3717, Folder 2)
  - NEA 115th Annual Meeting July 1-6, 1977: Tape II Hubert Humphrey, Series 1; Humphrey, Hubert H.; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS, 53 minutes long. (Box 3698, Folder 9)
  - NEA 115th Annual Meeting - Ryor & Herndon - Cassette Master Looped, 1977; Series 1; Ryor, John; Herndon, Terry; Magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. (Box 3688, Folder 2)
  - NEA 116th Annual Meeting (1978): John Ryor, Series 1; Ryor, John; Audio cassette. (Box 3682, Folder 29)
  - NEA 116th Annual Meeting - John Ryor Side 1; Terry Herndon Side 2 - Cassette master, Looped, 1978; Series 1; Herndon, Terry; Ryor, John; Magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. (Box 3688, Folder 1)
  - NEA Annual Meeting '78 - President John Ryor/Executive Director Terry Herndon - Slave, 1978; Series 1; Herndon, Terry; Ryor, John; Magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. (Box 3698, Folder 1)
  - NEA Annual Meeting - 1979: President John Ryor, Series 1; Audi cassette, 35 minutes. (Box 3682, Folder 23)
  - NEA Annual Meeting - 1980: NEA Pres. Willard McGuire; Pres. J. Carter, Series 1; McGuire, Willard H.; Carter, Jimmy, President, 1924-; Audio cassette, approx. 64 minutes. (Box 3682, Folder 24)
  - NEA Annual Meeting - 1981: ERA, Addie Wyatt; Friend of Education, George McGovern, Series 1; McGovern, George; Wyatt, Addie L., 1924-; Audio cassette, 64 minutes. (Box 3682, Folder 28)
  - NEA Annual Meeting - 1981: NEA President, Willard H. McGuire; NEA Exec. Dir. Terry Herndon, Series 1; McGuire, Willard H.; Herndon, Terry; Audio cassette, approx 67 minutes. (Box 3682, Folder 27)
  - NEA Annual Meeting - 1982: NEA Pres. Willard McGuire, Series 1; McGuire, Willard H.; Audi cassette, approx 42 minutes. (Box 3682, Folder 26)
  - NEA Annual Meeting - 1982: NEA Treasurer Mary Hatwood Futrell; NEA Exec. Dir. Terry Herndon, Series 1; Audio cassette, approx. 36 minutes. Two copies. (Box 3682, Folder 22)
  - NEA: Bahia Hotel, San Diego 1997, #1: Breakfast Session, 7:30 AM, May 15, 1997; Series 1; Audio cassette tape; two copies. (Box 3854, Folder 1)
  - NEA: Bahia Hotel, San Diego 1997, #2: General Session, 8:30 AM, May 15, 1997; Series 1; Audio cassette tape; two copies. (Box 3854, Folder 2)
  - NEA: Bahia Hotel, San Diego 1997, #3: General Session, 9:30 AM, May 15, 1997; Series 1; Audio cassette tape; two copies. (Box 3854, Folder 3)
  - NEA: Bahia Hotel, San Diego 1997, #4: General Session, 11:00 AM, May 15, 1997; Series 1; Audio cassette tape; two copies. (Box 3854, Folder 4)
  - NEA: Bahia Hotel, San Diego 1997, #5: General Session, Noon, May 15, 1997; Series 1; Audio cassette tape; two copies. (Box 3854, Folder 5)
  - NEA: Bahia Hotel, San Diego 1997, #6: Luncheon Session, 1:00 PM, May 15, 1997; Series 1; Audio cassette tape; two copies. (Box 3854, Folder 6)
  - NEA: Bahia Hotel, San Diego 1997, #7: General Session, 2:00 PM, May 15, 1997; Series 1; Audio cassette tape; two copies. (Box 3854, Folder 7)
  - NEA: Bahia Hotel, San Diego 1997, #8: General Session, 3:00 PM, May 15, 1997; Series 1; Audio cassette tape; two copies. (Box 3854, Folder 8)
  - NEA: Bahia Hotel, San Diego 1997, #9: Breakfast Session, 7:30 AM, May 16, 1997; Series 1; Audio cassette tape; two copies. (Box 3854, Folder 9)
  - NEA: Bahia Hotel, San Diego 1997, #10: General Session, 9:00 AM, May 16, 1997; Series 1; Audio cassette tape; two copies. (Box 3655, Folder 1)
  - NEA: Bahia Hotel, San Diego 1997, #11: General Session, 10:00 AM, May 16, 1997; Series 1; Audio cassette tape; two copies. (Box 3855, Folder 2)
  - NEA: Bahia Hotel, San Diego 1997, #12: General Session, 11:00 AM, May 16, 1997; Series 1; Audio cassette tape; two copies. (Box 3855, Folder 3)
  - NEA: Bahia Hotel, San Diego 1997, #13: General Session, Noon & Luncheon Session, 12:30 PM, May 16, 1997; Series 1; Audio cassette tape; two copies. (Box 3855, Folder 4)
  - NEA: Bahia Hotel, San Diego 1997, #14: Luncheon Session, 2:00 PM, May 16, 1997; Series 1; Audio cassette tape; two copies. (Box 3855, Folder 5)
  - NEA Convention #1 - Speeches Only - Political SN13734, undated; Series 1; Karex Silverchrome 5" helical scan video tape. No playback device available. (Box 3721, Folder 9)
  - NEA Convention #2 - Accountability - Saturday SN14168, undated; Series 1; Karex Silverchrome 5" helical scan video tape. No playback device available. (Box 3731, Folder 1)
  - NEA Convention #3 - SN 14160, undated; Series 1; Karex Silverchrome 5" helical scan video tape. No playback device available. (Box 3731, Folder 2)
  - NEA Convention #4 - SN14155, undated; Series 1; Karex Silverchrome 5" helical scan video tape. No playback device available. (Box 3731, Folder 3)
  - NEA Convention #5 - SN13741, undated; Series 1; Karex Silverchrome 5" helical scan video tape. No playback device available. (Box 3731, Folder 4)
  - NEA Convention #6 - Accountability - SN13779, undated; Series 1; Karex Silverchrome 5" helical scan video tape. No playback device available. (Box 3731, Folder 5)
  - NEA Convention #7 - SN13784, undated; Series 1; Karex Silverchrome 5" helical scan video tape. No playback device available. (Box 3731, Folder 6)
  - NEA Convention #8 - SN13773, undated; Series 1; Karex Silverchrome 5" helical scan video tape. No playback device available. (Box 3731, Folder 7)
  - NEA Convention #9 - SN13781, undated; Series 1; Karex Silverchrome 5" helical scan video tape. No playback device available. (Box 3731, Folder 9)
  - NEA Convention #13, undated; Series 1; Karex Silverchrome 5" helical scan video tape. No playback device available. (Box 3731, Folder 10)
  - NEA Convention #14 - I'm OK, You're OK 7/1/73, July 1, 1973; Series 1; Karex Silverchrome 5" helical scan video tape. No playback device available. (Box 3731, Folder 11)
  - NEA Convention #15, undated; Series 1; Karex Silverchrome 5" helical scan video tape. No playback device available. (Box 3741, Folder 1)
  - NEA Convention #16 - I'm OK, You're OK - Last Tape, undated; Series 1; Karex Silverchrome 5" helical scan video tape. No playback device available. (Box 3741, Folder 2)
  - NEA Convention #17 - Speeches, Not Full Roll, undated; Series 1; Karex Silverchrome 5" helical scan video tape. No playback device available. (Box 3741, Folder 3)
  - NEA Convention #19 - Political, June 30, 1973; Series 1; Silverchrome Karex (Box 3567, Folder 1)
  - NEA Convention #20 - Political, June 30, 1973; Series 1; Silverchrome Karex (Box 3558, Folder 10)
  - NEA Convention #27 - Student Rights, Undated; Series 1; Silverchrome Karex (Box 3558, Folder 11)
  - NEA Convention #28 - Spanish Saturday, Undated; Series 1; Silverchrome Karex (Box 3558, Folder 12)
  - NEA Convention #29 - Spanish, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3571, Folder 1)
  - NEA Convention #30 - Spanish, Undated; Series 1; Silverchrome Karex (Box 3572, Folder 1)
  - NEA Convention #31 - Spanish, Undated; Series 1; Silverchrome Karex (Box 3572, Folder 2)
  - NEA Convention High Lights 1963, Series 1; Magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. (Box 3687, Folder 6)
  - NEA Convention Highlights 1968 and NEA's Power at Work, Series 1; Magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. (Box 3687, Folder 4)
  - NEA Convention Highlights 1972, Series 1; Audio cassette. Soundtrack to filmstrip, but filmstrip was not included with cassette upon receipt. (Box 3682, Folder 40)
  - NEA COnvention (Reel 1), 1967; series 1 (Box 4520, Folder 1)
  - NEA Convention (Reel 2), 1967; series 1 (Box 4521, Folder 1)
  - NEA Convention Speakers, 1972: Lambert, Morrison, Barrett, Series 1; Audio cassette. Two copies. (Box 3682, Folder 30)
  - NEA Dedication, Reel 1: Auditorium/Statler, February 8, 1959; Series 1; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS for speech, 7 1/2 IPS for vocal. No available equipment to play this size reel. (Box 3829, Folder 2)
  - NEA Dedication, Reel 2: Auditorium/Hungarian Quartet, February 9, 1959; Series 1; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS side one, 7 1/2 IPS side two. No available equipment to play this size reel. (Box 3829, Folder 3)
  - NEA Convention (Real 3), 1967; series 1 (Box 4513, Folder 1)
  - NEA Dedication, Reel 3: 6th session/7th session, February 9-10, 1959; Series 1; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. No available equipment to play this size reel. (Box 3829, Folder 4)
  - NEA Dedication, Reel 4: 8th Session/9th Session, February 10, 1959; Series 1; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS side one; speech 3/34 IPS, music 7 1/2 IPS side two. No available equipment to play this size reel. (Box 3829, Folder 5)
  - NEA Convention Reel #1 ACT Saturday AM & Afternoon Meeting, June 26, 1971; Series 1; ½ Track Mono, 3 ¾ IPS reel-to-reel audio (Box 3934, Folder 4)
  - NEA Convention Reel #2 ACT Afternoon Session (Nominations), June 26, 1971; Series 1; ½ Track Mono, 3 ¾ IPS reel-to-reel audio (Box 3934, Folder 5)
  - NEA Convention Reel #3 ACT Saturday Afternoon Session (Wrap-up) & Evening Session (Opening), June 26, 1971; Series 1; ½ Track Mono, 3 ¾ IPS reel-to-reel audio (Box 3934, Folder 6)
  - NEA Convention Reel #4 ACT Saturday Evening Session, June 26, 1971; Series 1; ½ Track Mono, 3 ¾ IPS reel-to-reel audio (Box 3934, Folder 7)
  - NEA Convention Reel #5 ACT Saturday Evening Session & Sunday Afternoon Session (Opening), June 26-27, 1971; Series 1; ½ Track Mono, 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3934, Folder 8)
  - NEA Convention Reel #6 ACT Sunday Afternoon Session, June 27, 1971; Series 1; ½ Track Mono, 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3934, Folder 9)
  - NEA Convention Reel #7 ACT Saturday Evening Session & Sunday Afternoon Session & Evening Session (Opening), June 27, 1971; Series 1; ½ Track Mono, 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3934, Folder 10)
  - NEA Convention Reel #8 ACT Sunday Evening Session, June 27, 1971; Series 1; ½ Track Mono, 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3934, Folder 11)
  - NEA Convention Reel #9 ACT Sunday Evening Session, June 27, 1971; Series 1; ½ Track Mono, 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3934, Folder 12)
  - NEA Convention Reel #10 ACT Sunday Evening Session (Completion), June 27, 1971; Series 1; ½ Track Mono, 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3934, Folder 13)
  - NEA Executive Committee - Closed Session - Don Morrison 10/7/72, October 7, 1972; Series 1; Morrison, Donald E.; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 7 1/2 IPS. (Box 3771, Folder 9)
    Don Morrison's remarks and audience response from the closed door session of the Executive Committe which discussed Sam Lambert's resignation.
    Conditions Governing Access
    This collection is open for research. Tape was marked "Confidential," but is now open.
  - The NEA Foundation 2007 Gala- Award for Teaching Excellence Finalists, February 8, 2007; Series 1; DVD (Box 4015, Folder 2)
  - The NEA Foundation 2007 Gala- Award for Teaching Excellence Finalists, February 8, 2007; Series 1; DVD (Box 4015, Folder 3)
  - The NEA Foundation 2007 Gala- Award for Teaching Excellence Finalists, February 8, 2007; Series 1; DVD (Box 4015, Folder 4)
  - The NEA Foundation 2007 Gala- Award for Teaching Excellence Finalists, February 8, 2007; Series 1; DVD (Box 4015, Folder 5)
  - The NEA Foundation 2007 Gala- Award for Teaching Excellence Finalists, February 8, 2007; Series 1; DVD (Box 4015, Folder 6)
  - The NEA Foundation 2007 Gala- Award for Teaching Excellence Finalists, February 8, 2007; Series 1; DVD (Box 4015, Folder 7)
  - The NEA Foundation 2007 Gala- Award for Teaching Excellence Finalists, February 8, 2007; Series 1; DVD (Box 4015, Folder 8)
  - NEA Officials 1976: Ryor/Herndon, Series 1; Audio cassette. Tension pad is detached and tape will not play. (Box 3682, Folder 42)
  - NEA Officials 1976: Ryor/Herndon Looped Master, Series 1; Herndon, Terry; Ryor, John; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. (Box 3717, Folder 3)
  - NEA Highlights 1969, Series 1; Magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. (Box 3687, Folder 3)
  - NEA Highlights, 1967, Series 1; Magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. (Box 3687, Folder 5)
  - NEA-PAC Council Meeting: Vice President Walter Mondale, 4/30/1981, April 30, 1981; Series 1; Mondale, Walter F.; Audio cassette. (Box 3682, Folder 32)
  - NEA-PAC Giveaway B-Roll, July 3, 1992; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3995, Folder 8)
  - NEA-PAC RA Video 1997, Hune 20, 1997; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 21)
  - NEA President Keith Geiger Address at 1992 NEA R.A., July 14, 1992; Series 1; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 8)
  - NEA President's Keith Geiger's Address: 1994 NEA R.A., July 21, 1994; Series 1; 16mm film (Box 4028, Folder 4)
  - NEA Professional Library Product Promotion, 1993; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3995, Folder 9)
  - NEA Professional Library Promotions, 1994; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3995, Folder 10)
  - The NEA Representative Assembly "How It Works", May 11, 2001; Series 1 (Box 4635, Folder 1)
  - NEA Resolutons Committee - Bernie Freitag, Vice President - March 6-9, 1980, Series 1; Freitag, Bernie; Magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. (Box 3688, Folder 5)
  - NEA Resolutons Committee - Terry Herndon, Exec. Dir. - March 6-9, 1980, Series 1; Herndon, Terry; Magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. (Box 3688, Folder 6)
  - NEA State Association Conference 1963 Denver - James Russell - The Ethical Dimension, Series 1 (Box 3572, Folder 3)
  - NEA State Association Conference 1963 Denver - James Russell - The Ethical Dimension - 3:35 Master, Series 1 (Box 3572, Folder 4)
  - NEA/TTV K.G. Pacific Regional Conf., February 10, 1994; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4024, Folder 5)
  - NEA/TTV K.G. Pacific Regional Conference for 2/25/94, February 10, 1994; Series 1; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 5)
  - New Dynamics in Curriculum and Teaching - Ole Sands Group TCM Box 1, Undated; Series 1; 7 ½ IPS reel-to-reel audio (Box 3908, Folder 8)
  - New Dynamics in Curriculum and Teaching - Ole Sands Group TCM Box 2 Overlap Dub, Undated; Series 1; 7 ½ IPS reel-to-reel audio (Box 3908, Folder 9)
  - New York Project - Shanker 2/2/76 Sub-master Looped, February 2, 1976; Series 3; Shanker, Albert; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. (Box 3717, Folder 4)
  - Non-Delegate/Delegate Registration Area, July 4, 1992; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3996, Folder 1)
  - North Central Regional Conference on Instruction - Dubridge, Lee - The Teaching Profession, undated; Series 1; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. (Box 3751, Folder 5)
  - North Central Regional Conference on Instruction - Hyer, Fri AM, undated; Series 1; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. Includes printed outline. (Box 3751, Folder 6)
  - North Central Regional Conference on Instruction - Suchman, undated; Series 1; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. (Box 3751, Folder 7)
  - Panetta's Speech, September 22, 1995; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4100, Folder 2)
  - "Physical Science" – Rose Lammel – Prof. of Science Educ., Wayne State U. Tuesday, March 27, 1:30 pm, Undated; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3884, Folder 6)
  - Political Group Disc - NEA Convention # 18, Undated; Series 1; Silverchrome Karex (Box 3572, Folder 5)
  - President Clinton at NEA Representative Assembly, San Francisco, CA, July 5, 1993; Series 1; BETACAM video tapes (Box 3990, Folder 6)
  - President Clinton at NEA Representative Assembly San Francisco, CA, July 5, 1993; Series 1 (Box 4100, Folder 3)
  - President Clinton - NEA National Conference - School Safety - L.A., April, 1995; Series 1 (Box 3990, Folder 7)
  - President Clinton NEA National Conference - School Safety - L.A., April, 1995; Series 1 (Box 4100, Folder 4)
  - President Geiger's Speech - NEA RA 1993, San Francisco, CA, Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3976, Folder 7)
  - "Programming" – P. Kenneth Komoski, Pres., Center for Programmed Instruction, NYC Wednesday, March 28, 10:00 am, Undated; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3884, Folder 8)
  - RA Finale Show "Team NEA", July 5, 2003; Series 1 (Box 4635, Folder 2)
  - R.A. Demonstration Tape, July 8, 1992; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3996, Folder 2)
  - Rept. Assbly. AIDS Quilt Celebration 1993, Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3989, Folder 9)
  - Sadtu A Celebration: South African Democratic Teachers Union Hosted by Bob Chase B-3 Auditorium, October 18, 2001; Series 1 (Box 4635, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of State Richard W. Riley - Board of Directors Meeting, October 16, 1993; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4100, Folder 5)
  - Senator Paul Wellstone NEA's 2003 Friend of Education Award Education Minnesota, Series 1 (Box 4635, Folder 4)
  - Sights and Sounds - Music Educators National Conference in Covention, September 1968; Series 1; Pre-Recorded Program Film 7 1/2 IPS (Box 3667, Folder 1)
    Separated materials found in Box 3662 File 12 Filmstrip
  - Sharon M. Draper - 97 Teacher of the Year - 1997 NEA RA Address, Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3975, Folder 6)
  - Spokane Regional Conference, 1966 Anna L. Hyer, Series 1; reel-to-reel audio tape (Box 3871, Folder 2)
  - Spokane Regional Conference, 1966 "Design for Improvement of Education" Leon P. Minnear, Series 1; reel-to-reel audio tape (Box 3871, Folder 6)
  - Spokane Regional Conference, 1966 "Determining What We Teach" Elizabeth Koontz and George D. Brain, Series 1; reel-to-reel audio tape (Box 3871, Folder 3)
  - Spokane Regional Conference, 1966 Elizabeth Koontz and George D. Brain [1/2], Series 1; reel-to-reel audio tape (Box 3871, Folder 4)
  - Spokane Regional Conference, 1966 Elizabeth Koontz and George D. Brain [2/2], Series 1; reel-to-reel audio tape (Box 3871, Folder 5)
  - Spokane Regional Conference, 1966 "Inquiry and Teaching", Series 1; reel-to-reel audio tape (Box 3871, Folder 1)
  - Spokane Regional Conference, 1966 James A. Russell [1/2], Series 1; reel-to-reel audio tape (Box 3871, Folder 9)
  - Spokane Regional Conference, 1966 James A. Russell [2/2], Series 1; reel-to-reel audio tape (Box 3871, Folder 10)
  - Spokane Regional Conference - 1966 - Margaret S. Woods # 5 Side 1 - M. Woods - Demonstration not on order form, Series 1; Side 1 x 2 3/4 (Box 3572, Folder 6)
  - Spokane Regional Conference, 1966 Leon P. Minnear [1/2], Series 1; reel-to-reel audio tape (Box 3871, Folder 7)
  - Spokane Regional Conference, 1966 Leon P. Minnear [2/2], Series 1; reel-to-reel audio tape (Box 3871, Folder 8)
  - Spokane Regional Conference, 1966 Ole Sand, Series 1; reel-to-reel audio tape (Box 3871, Folder 11)
  - Spokane Regional Conference, 1966 "Our Challenge: New Federal Legislation" J. Richard Suchman, Series 1; reel-to-reel audio tape (Box 3871, Folder 12)
  - Spokane Regional Conference, 1966 "Use of TV in the In-Service Education of Teachers" Harold E. Wigren, Series 1; reel-to-reel audio tape (Box 3871, Folder 13)
  - Spokane Regional Confernce on Inst. J, Richard Sushman - Our Challange - New Federal Legislation - Master - Panelists - Jeannette Moorhead, Ruth R. Chandler. James M. Thrasher, Donald R. Kruzner, Undated; Series 1; 3 3/4 IPS Full Track (Box 3572, Folder 7)
  - State Assn. - Denver 1963 - NEA and State Association Conference Dr. Lyman Ginger - Master, Series 1; 3-3/4 1.85 (Box 3572, Folder 8)
    Ginger, Lyman Vernon
  - State Assn. - Denver 1963 - NEA Regional Conference - Elizabeth Drew "Pupil Values and Self Actualization" - Master, Series 1; 2:35 3 3/4 (Box 3572, Folder 9)
  - State Assn. - Denver 1963 - NEA Regional Conference - J. Richard Sushman "The Nature of Intelligence & The Learning Process" - Elaslewood, Colo., Series 1; DOI 050 LV. 8 Master 2:35 Use almost full 7" Reel (Box 3572, Folder 10)
  - State Assn. - Denver 1963 - NEA Regional Confernce - Margaret S. Wood "Creativity in Teaching" Master, Series 1; 2.35 (Box 3572, Folder 11)
  - State Assn. - Denver 1963 - NEA Regional Conference - "Ole Sand - New Perspective for Schools in the Sixties" - Master, Series 1; 3-3/4 2.35 (Box 3572, Folder 12)
  - Study Team Meeting, Nov. 5-6, 1965: Tape 1, November 5-6, 1965; Series 1; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 1 7/8 IPS. (Box 3856, Folder 1)
  - Study Team Meeting, Nov. 5-6, 1965: Tape 3, November 5-6, 1965; Series 1; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 1 7/8 IPS. (Box 3856, Folder 2)